/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data4_1', {
    title: '4.1 Mean, Median, Mode',
    path: '4.1-mean-median-mode',
    children: [{
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the average for these values:<br>127, 76, 22, 28, 32.}',
                answer: '\\input{57}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>(127 + 76 + 22 + 28 + 32) ÷ 5 = 57}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the average for these values:<br>93, 60, 30, 33.}',
                answer: '\\input{54}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>(93 + 60 + 30 + 33) ÷ 4 = 54}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the average for these values:<br>118, 16, 52.}',
                answer: '\\input{62}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>(118 + 16 + 52) ÷ 3 = 62}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the median for these values:<br>458, 229, 310, 728, 661, 342.}',
                answer: '\\input{400}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\html{Solution<br><br>229 310 <span class=red>342 458</span> 661 728<br><br>Sort the numbers in ascending order. Then select the middle number. If there are two middle numbers, take their average. The average of 342 and 458 is 400.}}{help_4-1}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the median for these values:<br>714, 689, 639, 589, 533.}',
                answer: '\\input{639}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\html{Solution<br><br>533 589 <span class=red>639</span> 689 714<br><br>Sort the numbers in ascending order. Then select the middle number. If there are two middle numbers, take their average.}}{help_4-1}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the median for these values:<br>118, 333, 690, 417.}',
                answer: '\\input{375}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\html{Solution<br><br>118 <span class=red>333 417</span> 690<br><br>Sort the numbers in ascending order. Then select the middle number. If there are two middle numbers, take their average. The average of 333 and 417 is 375.}}{help_4-1}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the mode(s) for these values:<br>465, 465, 534, 557, 557.<br><br>If the numbers have no mode, enter "none".<br>If there is more than one mode, enter them in ascending order.}',
                answer: '\\css{grp{\\input{[465,557]}}{\\input{[557,465]}}}{mode}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\html{Solution<br><br><span class=red>465 465</span> 534 <span class=red>557 557</span><br><br>Sort the numbers in ascending order. Then select the number or numbers that appear most frequently.The mode is: 465 & 557.}}{help_4-1}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the mode(s) for these values:<br>294, 406, 200, 564.<br><br>If the numbers have no mode, enter "none". If there is more than one mode, enter them in ascending order.}',
                answer: '\\input{none}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>200 294 406 564<br><br>Sort the numbers in ascending order. Then select the number or numbers that appear most frequently.The mode is: none because no numbers appear more than once.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the mode(s) for these values:<br>540, 540, 439, 41, 259, 690.<br><br>If the numbers have no mode, enter "none". If there is more than one mode, enter them in ascending order.}',
                answer: '\\input{540}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\html{Solution<br><br>41 259 439 <span class=red>540 540</span> 690<br><br>Sort the numbers in ascending order. Then select the number or numbers that appear most frequently.The mode is: 540.}}{help_4-1}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the median for these values:<br>409, 434, 416, 129, 550, 448.}',
                answer: '\\input{425}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\html{Solution<br><br>129 409 <span class=red>416 434</span> 448 550<br><br>Sort the numbers in ascending order. Then select the middle number. If there are two middle numbers, take their average. The average of 416 and 434 is 425.}}{help_4-1}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the mode(s) for these values:<br>400, 400, 319, 438, 398.<br><br>If the numbers have no mode, enter "none". If there is more than one mode, enter them in ascending order.}',
                answer: '\\input{400}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\html{Solution<br><br>319 398 <span class=red>400 400</span> 438<br><br>Sort the numbers in ascending order. Then select the number or numbers that appear most frequently.The mode is: 400.}}{help_4-1}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the average for these values:<br><br>61, 121, 14, 28.}',
                answer: '\\input{56}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>(61 + 121 + 14 + 28) ÷ 4 = 56}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the mode(s) for these values:<br>763, 115, 113, 119, 761, 763.<br><br>If the numbers have no mode, enter "none". If there is more than one mode, enter them in ascending order.}',
                answer: '\\input{763}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\html{Solution<br><br>113 115 119 761 <span class=red>763 763</span><br><br>Sort the numbers in ascending order. Then select the number or numbers that appear most frequently.The mode is: 763.}}{help_4-1}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the average for these values:<br><br>74, 96, 24, 14.}',
                answer: '\\input{52}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br>(74 + 96 + 24 + 14) ÷ 4 = 52}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Mean, Median, or Mode',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Determine the median for these values:<br>585, 358, 766, 528, 582.}',
                answer: '\\input{582}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\css{\\html{Solution<br><br>358 528 <span class=red>582</span> 585 766<br><br>Sort the numbers in ascending order. Then select the middle number. If there are two middle numbers, take their average.}}{help_4-1}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, ]
});
